<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PhotoShare</string>

    <string name="dummy_button">About</string>
    <string name="ok_button">OK</string>
    <string name="dummy_content"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">About PhotoShare</string>
    <string name="large_text">
       "\n\nWe are a photography website that allows users to create profiles, upload and share unlimited photos, seek photography advice, critique other users' photos, and compete in contests. We are a Vancouver based startup and we've launched the beta version of this site in August 2015, with the Founder as the only employee of the company. Currently, the site is solely managed, developed, and operated by Tony Wei; however, it is certainly a possibility that PhotoShare will be hiring additional employees on board in the near future!

Our website is seen as a community where aspiring photographers, both amateur and professional, can share their work with the world, seek photography advice in order to improve, and join weekly competitions to compare their work with others. As of today, we currently have a rapidly growing user base, with more signing up in the past month than in the last quarter of 2015! There are also multiple premium features users can access after upgrading their account (a one-time fee of $10 Canadian dollars), such as unlimited uploads, unlimited photo advice requests, participating in photo competitions, and website user interface customizations. Please sign up today to receive a limited-time offer of 14 days of FREE PhotoShare Premium upgrade! The website is available in both English as well as Simplified Chinese.
    \n

Our website features a home page where all the popular photos are displayed, such as most liked, most commented, recently uploaded, and even highest competition scored. One major feature of the site is the Learn and Improve page where free users can request up to 10 photography-related advices per day and premium users have unlimited requests. Another feature is the ability for special users, called chairmen, to initiate photo competitions in which premium users can submit their photos to, and certified judges can give these photos a score out of 10. The winner of the competition can win prizes. Users of Photoshare are able to log in without registering an account by linking their Facebook account.\n\n\n\n\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
